<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NewsApp</string>

    <string-array name="science">
    <item>Microsoft, Facebook to jointly build subsea cable for faster internet. </item>
    <item>Facebook set to overhaul "Trending Topics".</item>
    <item>Third-gen Formula E-car that zips to 220 kmph, unveiled in Berlin.  </item>
    <item>Apple CEO Tim Cook meets Bharti Airtel Chief Mittal.</item>
    <item>Apple opens development centre for Digital Maps in Hyderabad.</item>
    <item >Pichai unveils Google Assistant to help with daily tasks. </item>
    <item>We are in India for the next thousand years, says Apple boss Tim Cook.</item>
    <item>Apple announces iOS App Design and development accelerator in Bangaluru.</item>
    <item>India successfully test-fires advanced interceptor missile.</item>
    <item>One Plus 3 to be launched on a virtual space station with a new loop VR headset.</item>
    <item>Returning to the flip-phone era with Moto Razr.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="states">
    <item>Cops to deploy state-of-the-art command vehicle for IPL final on Sunday. </item>
    <item>School Bag: Heaviest burden for unaided schools.</item>
    <item>Governor again rejects S.R.Nayak name for Lokyukta post.  </item>
    <item>1500 registrations for fourth edition of Super Mom.</item>
    <item>No state-quota medical seats for in COMEDK colleges.</item>
    <item>RS polls: Congress to field third candidate, hopes to benefit from JD(s) infighting.</item>
    <item>Doctors report a spike in cases of viral fever among children.</item>
    <item>From July visas with multiple entry points to Australia to be available.</item>
    <item>Re-evaluation: change in criterion for awarding revised marks for PCB.</item>
    <item>Congress to finalise RS Council poll candidates today.</item>
    <item>Income Tax officer gets bail in bribery case.</item>
    <item>Proposal for anti-sea erosion wall to be sent to government.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sports">
    <item>Rafael Nadal pulls out of French Open with wrist injury.</item>
    <item>Turning to doubles to sustain a professional career.</item>
    <item>England wins toss, bats in second test against Sri Lanks.</item>
    <item>Does the fate of the team lies in the hands of the coach.</item>
    <item>Unsuited to the limited-overs game? Say what, asks Rahul.</item>
    <item>Hafeez likely to be sent to England for treatement:PCB.</item>
    <item>Lions batsmen vs sunrisers bowlers, the defining contest of Qualifiers-2 .</item>
    <item>Warners praises bowlers, fielders for win over KKR.</item>
    <item>Steeped down because I could not see the board being destroyed, says Shashank Manohar.</item>
    <item>FIFA sacks finance director Markus Kattner over bonus payments.</item>
    <item>Sad that Platini ban remains: FIFA director Infantino.</item>
    <item>We are not underdogs anymore:Manpreet.</item>
    <item>Raghunath, Dharamveer, Ritu nominated ofr Arjuna Award.</item>
    <item>Hockey team returns with Silver from Azlan Shah Cup.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="national">
    <item>Supreme Court declines to put NEET Ordinance on hold.</item>
    <item>BJP has delievered on decisive government:Amit Shah.</item>
    <item>Attack on Nigerian student:Sushma seeks report from KCR.</item>
    <item>Northeast is a gateway for SoutheastAsia:Modi at NEC meet at Shillong.</item>
    <item>PAC takes up CAG report on AugustaWestland issue.</item>
    <item>Eleven members of a family killed in a road mishap in rajasthan.</item>
    <item>Two security personnel injured in gunbattle in Baramulla.</item>
    <item>Agusta Westland documents in CBI custody, cannot be disclosed:CIC.</item>
    <item>Pranab stresses people centric partnership between India and China.</item>
    <item>Government is accountable, pro-poor, says Narendra Modi.</item>
    <item>Stray Nilgai damages police vehicle near Parliament House.</item>
    <item>Stress on need to adapt scientific, technological innovations.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="international">
    <item>Donald Trump promises to cancel Paris climate agreement.</item>
    <item>Obama offers tribute but no apology at Hiroshima.</item>
    <item>Delay Olympics or move it out of Rio, say experts.</item>
    <item>Mendela drivers among first to receive bequests from will.</item>
    <item>Referendum debate spoilt by misinformation:parliamentory committee.</item>
    <item>Pakistan should completely stop support to terror to boost ties, PM.</item>
    <item>Final vote on Dilma impeachment could come 3 days before Olympics.</item>
    <item>Two yojng India-Americas win US Spelling Bee in historic tie.</item>
    <item>Pentagon will do whatever is needed to protect its forces.</item>
    <item>Taliban strikes sign of US exasperation with Pakistan duplicity.</item>
    <item>France: Day of strikes, protests, fuel blockades over labour bill.</item>
    <item>Sri Lanka panel gives approval fro pre-fabricated steel houses.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="entertainment">
    <item>As long as music touches one soul, musicians are secure.</item>
    <item>Shashank Subramaniyam talks of his music influences.</item>
    <item>Censor Board works as per government rules:Bachchan.</item>
    <item>I am a psycho-thriller loyalist, says Pawan Kriplani.</item>
    <item>Devotional vibes on Annamayya birth anniversary.</item>
    <item>Thinking outside the LunchBox.</item>
    <item>Sedates and sonorous singing.</item>
    <item>Play of mudras and melody.</item>
    <item>Gamchhas transformed into saris.</item>
    <item>The Angry Birds movie: Does not take off.</item>
    <item>Veerappan: The film life belongs to Muthulakshmi.</item>
    <item>Waiting: On the pause before a loss.</item>
    <item>A lot to laugh, little to reflect.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="business">
    <item>India is an untapped Economy:Nikki Haley.</item>
    <item>Our aim is to generate 20% RoE: Motilal Oswal.</item>
    <item>Anantha Radhakrishnan is new MD of Infosys BPO.</item>
    <item>Morgan stanley marks down Flipkart values once again.</item>
    <item>Jaitley to meet key investors during 6-day Japan visit.</item>
    <item>Rupee strengthens to 1-week high, up 14 paise to 67.03.</item>
    <item>Rajan appointment should not be of media interest:Modi.</item>
    <item>Foreign investors reduce holdings in top 200 companies in March quarter.</item>
    <item>Centre may approve import of unshredded metal scrap in Raipur.</item>
    <item>Maruti to recall over 75000 Balenos nearly 2000 DZires.</item>
    <item>Wipro CEO got $1.8 million as salary in last fiscal year.</item>
    <item>SBI Q4 net falls 66 percent.</item>
    <item>Norms soon to weed out fraud in staffing industry.</item>
    <item>Tech Mahindra to acquire U.K based Target Group.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
